A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission, RG 6 FA787
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files, 1955-1962; 8; 3.51 Cubic Feet 8 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
  - Commercial Organizations, 1958-1961 (Box 20, Folder 224)
  - Controversy - National Forest and National Park Sevice, 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Demography, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Economic Evaluations and Analysis, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - Education, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - Employee Recreation, 1959-1961 (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Encroachment Affairs, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 230)
  - Erosion, 1961 May (Box 21, Folder 231)
  - Facilities, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 232)
  - Farming and Related Affairs, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 233)
  - Federal Lands and Waters, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 234)
  - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 235)
  - "Field and Stream", 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 236)
  - Films, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 237)
  - Fishery, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 238)
  - Forecasts, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 239)
  - Forest Preserve, 1958-1962 (Box 21, Folder 240)
  - Garden Clubs, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 241)
  - Highways, 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 242)
  - Indian Affairs, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 243)
  - Inspection Areas, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 244)
  - Institute for Public Administration, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 245)
  - Inventory Data, 1957-1961 (Box 22, Folder 246)
  - Investment Suggestions, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 247)
  - Juvenile Playgrounds, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 248)
  - Local Area Problems, 1958-1962 (Box 22, Folder 249-251)
  - Lumbering Practices, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 252)
  - Medical and Health Affairs, 1955-1961 (Box 23, Folder 253)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 254)
  - Mining Interests, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 255)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1962 (Box 23, Folder 256)
  - National Planning Association, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 257)
  - Natural Lands Trust, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 258)
  - Natural Resources - U.S., 1960 (Box 23, Folder 259)
  - News Releases, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 260)
  - Newspaper Correspondence, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 261)
  - Objectives and Recommendations, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 262)
  - Open Space Land, 1961 June 30 (Box 24, Folder 263)
  - Pest Control, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 264)
  - Philosophy of Recreation, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 265)
  - Policy Issues, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 266)
  - Pollution Problems, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - President of the U.S., 1958-1962 (Box 24, Folder 268-269)
  - President's Council on Youth Fitness, 1957-1962 (Box 24, Folder 270-271)
  - Program and Policy Objectives, 1958-1961 (Box 25, Folder 272)
  - Public Relations, 1958-1962 (Box 25, Folder 273-275)
  - Public Use of Private Land, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 276)
  - Publications Program, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 277)
  - Quotations - Conservation, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 278)
  - Recreation Sites, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 279)
  - Reservoir Affairs, 1961-1962 (Box 25, Folder 280)
  - Seminars, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 281)
  - Shoreline Preservation, 1959-1961 (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 263)
  - Study Plans, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 264-265)
  - Study Reports, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 266)
  - Tasks and Activities, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 267)
  - Time Schedules for Publications, 1959-1961 (Box 26, Folder 268)
  - Transportation, 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Universities, 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - Universities - Harvard - Land Use and Conservation, 1959-1962 (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - Universities - Wayne State - Program Proposal, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - Water Use and Preservation, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 273)
  - Wetlands, 1962 March-October (Box 26, Folder 274)
  - White House Conference on Conservation, 1962 May 24-25 (Box 26, Folder 275)
  - Wilderness, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 276)
  - Wilderness Bill, 1957-1959 (Box 27, Folder 277)
  - Wilderness Bill, 1960-1962 (Box 27, Folder 278)
  - Wilderness Society, 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 279)
  - Wildlife Management Institute, 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 280)
  - Wildlife Preservation and Hunting, 1958-1962 (Box 27, Folder 281)
  - Williams, Senator Harrison A., 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 282)
- Meetings, 1958-1962; 9; 2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
  This series contains agendas and transcripts of meetings held by the Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission, including meetings with the National Park Service and the Commission's Advisory Council. There is also a small amount of correspondence relating to meeting activities at the end of the series.
  - Meeting, 1958 September 25 (Box 27, Folder 283)
  - Meeting, 1958 November 11-12 (Box 27, Folder 284)
  - Meeting, 1959 January 20-21 (Box 27, Folder 285)
  - Meeting, 1959 March 23 (Box 28, Folder 286)
  - Meeting, 1959 May 12 (Box 28, Folder 287)
  - Advisory Council Joint Meeting, 1959 July 16-17 (Box 28, Folder 288)
  - Meeting, 1959 August 10 (Box 28, Folder 289)
  - Meeting, 1959 October 20 (Box 28, Folder 290)
  - Meeting, 1959 December 14-15 (Box 28, Folder 291-292)
  - Regional Meetings, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 293)
  - Advisory Council Joint Meeting, 1960 January 25-26 (Box 28, Folder 294)
  - Meeting, 1960 May 25 (Box 29, Folder 295-296)
  - Advisory Council Joint Meeting, 1960 July 29 - August 4 (Box 29, Folder 297-299, Box 30, Folder 300)
  - Meeting, 1960 August 1-2 (Box 30, Folder 301)
  - Meeting, 1960 December 12-14 (Box 30, Folder 302-303)
  - National Park Service Staff Meeting, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 304)
  - Meeting, 1961 February 2-3 (Box 30, Folder 305)
  - Meeting, 1961 March 12 (Box 30, Folder 306)
  - Advisory Council Joint Meeting, 1961 March 13-14 (Box 30, Folder 307, Box 31, Folder 308)
  - Meeting, 1961 April 25-26 (Box 31, Folder 309)
  - Meeting, 1961 May 22 (Box 31, Folder 310)
  - Meeting, 1961 June 26-27 (Box 31, Folder 311-312)
  - Meeting, 1961 July 27-28 (Box 31, Folder 313-314)
  - Meeting, 1961 September 25-28 (Box 31, Folder 315)
  - Meeting, 1961 October 12-14 (Box 32, Folder 316)
  - Meeting, 1961 November 28-29 (Box 32, Folder 317-318)
  - Meeting, 1962 January 29 (Box 32, Folder 319)
  - Meeting, 1962 November 11 (Box 32, Folder 320)
  - General Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 32, Folder 321)
- Clippings, 1962; 10; 0.94 Cubic Feet 2 legal document boxes
  - Clippings, 1962 March - October (Box 33, Folder 322-324)
  - Clippings, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 325-326)
  - Presentation of ORRRC Report, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 327-328)
  - Non-Outdoor Columns, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 329)
  - AP Newsfeature Article, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 330)
  - Kennedy Message on Natural Resources, Recreation, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 331)